<Grid>
<Body>
<B>
<I id='B' Def='Desc' NoColorState='1' A='Books' GCanFocus='0' GRowSpan='' BType='Radio' BAlign='center' MaxHeight='' 
   BEnum='|&lt;span style="font-weight:700;color:#0C0;">read only&lt;/span>|&lt;span style="font-weight:700;color:#0C0;">edit values&lt;/span>' B='0' BCanEdit='1'>
<I id='B1' A='The Art of Superman Returns' B='|Daniel Wallace|Daniel Wallace' C='Chronicle Books LLC' D='6/30/2006' E='160' F='0811853446' G='40' H='0'>
   <I id='B1D' Def='Desc' G='|Books.jpg|75|65|480|0|http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0811853446/ref=amb_left-5_185406401_1/104-5992118-7327169?n=283155|_blank' B="The Man of Steel is back on the silver screen when Superman Returns hits theaters June 2006. Directed by Bryan Singer (X-Men) and packed with explosive action, this blockbuster film documents the super hero's return-after a mysterious absence of several years-to a troubled Metropolis, where he is compelled to face his destiny in a world that has forgotten what it's like to have a hero. The Art of Superman Returns is an in-depth celebration of the concept and developmental art that served as an aesthetic foundation for the highly anticipated film. Nearly 200 pieces of gorgeous art capture all-new sets-a cosmopolitan, art deco Metropolis, a massive, shimmering Fortress of Solitude, and a spectacular spaceship-and showcase the film's inventive costumes and breathtaking locations. An informed text that includes interviews with the director, screenwriters, artists, and production and costume designers completes this thoughtfully crafted deluxe hardcover. For the many Superman fans anxiously awaiting his revival, The Art of Superman Returns is a behind-the-scenes tour not to be missed."/>
   <I id='B1I' Def='Info' A='About the author' B='Daniel Wallace is the author of more than a dozen books, including the The DC Comics Encyclopedia and the New York Times best-seller Star Wars: The New Essential Guide to Characters . He lives in Detroit.'/>
</I>
<I id='B2' A='Fiske Guide to Colleges 2007' B='|Edward Fiske|Edward Fiske' C='Sourcebooks, Inc.' D='7/9/2006' E='800' F='1402206607' G='22.95' H='1'>
   <I id='B2D' Def='Desc' G='|Books.jpg|59|75|560|0|http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/1402206607/ref=amb_left-2_185402901_1/104-5992118-7327169?n=283155|_blank' B="For more than 20 years, this leading guide to more than 300 colleges and universities has been an indispensable source of information for college-bound students and their parents. Hip, honest and straightforward, the Fiske Guide to Colleges delivers an insider's look at the academic climates and the social and extracurricular scenes at the &quot;best and most interesting&quot; schools in the U.S., plus Canada and Great Britain.&#x0A;&#x0A;Includes:&#x0A;-- Fiske's exclusive academic, social and quality-of-life ratings&#x0A;-- The 40+ schools that deliver the best education at the most reasonable costs&#x0A;-- Lists of each school's strongest majors and programs&#x0A;-- Candid tips from each school's current students&#x0A;-- A self-quiz to help understand which college is right for a student&#x0A;-- Vital information on how to apply&#x0A;-- &quot;Overlap&quot; listings to help students expand their options&#x0A;-- Selectivity statistics and SAT and ACT ranges"/>
   <I id='B2I' Def='Info' A='About the author' B='Edward B. Fiske served for 17 years as Education Editor of The New York Times, during which time he realized that college-bound students and their families needed better information on which to base their educational choices. He is the author of the bestselling annual, The Fiske Guide to Colleges and The Fiske Guide to Getting into the Right College. He lives in Durham, North Carolina, near the campus of Duke University.'/>
</I>
<I id='B3' A='Only Revolutions' B='|Mark Z. Danielewsky|Mark Z. Danielewsky' C='Pantheon' D='9/5/2006' E='284' F='0375421769' G='26' H='0'>
   <I id='B3D' Def='Desc' G='|Books.jpg|43|75|240|0|http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0375421769/ref=amb_left-1_185398801_1/104-5992118-7327169?n=283155|_blank' B="Sam:&#x0A;They were with us before Romeo &amp; Juliet. And long after too. Because they&apos;re forever around. Or so both claim, carolling gleefully:&#x0A;We&apos;re allways sixteen.&#x0A;Sam &amp; Hailey, powered by an ever-rotating fleet of cars, from Model T to Lincoln Continental, career from the Civil War to the Cold War, barrelling down through the Appalachians, up the Mississippi River, across the Badlands, finally cutting a nation in half as they try to outrace History itself.&#x0A;By turns beguiling and gripping, finally worldwrecking, Only Revolutions is unlike anything ever published before, a remarkable feat of heart and intellect, moving us with the journey of two kids, perpetually of summer, perpetually sixteen, who give up everything except each other.&#x0A;&#x0A;Hailey:&#x0A;They were with us before Tristan &amp; Isolde. And long after too. Because they&apos;re forever around. Or so both claim, gleefully carolling:&#x0A;We&apos;re allways sixteen.&#x0A;Hailey &amp; Sam, powered by an ever-rotating fleet of cars, from Shelby Mustang to Sumover Linx, careen from the Civil Rights Movement to the Iraq War, tearing down to New Orleans, up the Mississippi River, across Montana, finally cutting a nation in half as they try to outrace History itself.&#x0A;By turns enticing and exhilarating, finally breathtaking, Only Revolutions is unlike anything ever conceived before, a remarkable feat of heart and intellect, moving us with the journey of two kids, perpetually of summer, perpetually sixteen, who give up everything except each other.&#x0A;"/>
   <I id='B3I' Def='Info' A='About the author' B='Mark Z. Danielewski was born in New York City and now lives in Los Angeles. He is the author of House of Leaves.'/>
</I>
<I id='B4' A='Twelve Sharp' B='|Janet Evanovich|Janet Evanovich' C='St. Martin&apos;s Press' D='6/20/2006' E='320' F='0312349483' G='26.95' H='0'>
   <I id='B4D' Def='Desc' G='|Books.jpg|49|75|0|0|http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0312349483/ref=amb_right-1_168832101_1/104-5992118-7327169?n=283155|_blank' B='Welcome to Trenton, New Jersey, where bounty hunter Stephanie Plum&apos;s life is about to implode in Janet Evanovich&apos;s wildest, hottest novel yet!&#x0A;&#x0A;FIRST A STRANGER APPEARS&#x0A;While chasing down the usual cast of miscreants and weirdos Stephanie discovers that a crazed woman is stalking her.&#x0A;&#x0A;THEN THE STRANGER REVEALS HER SECRETS&#x0A;The woman dresses in black, carries a 9mm Glock, and has a bad attitude and a mysterious connection to dark and dangerous Carlos Manoso ...street name, Ranger.&#x0A;&#x0A;NEXT, SOMEBODY DIES&#x0A;The action turns deadly serious, and Stephanie goes from hunting skips to hunting a murderer.&#x0A;&#x0A;SOON, THE CHASE IS ON&#x0A;Ranger needs Stephanie for more reasons than he can say.  And now, the two are working together to find a killer, rescue a missing child, and stop a lunatic from raising the body count.  When Stephanie Plum and Ranger get too close for comfort, vice cop Joe Morelli (her on-again, off-again boyfriend) steps in.&#x0A;&#x0A;Will the ticking clock stop at the stroke of twelve, or will a stranger in the wind find a way to stop Stephanie Plum...forever?  Filled with Janet Evanovich&apos;s trademark action, nonstop adventure, and sharp humor, Twelve Sharp shows why her novels have been called "hot stuff" (The New York Times), and Evanovich herself "the master" (San Francisco Examiner).'/>
   <I id='B4I' Def='Info' A='From Publishers Weekly' B="The mixture of slapstick and gunplay that has put Evanovich's series about a sassy, less than competent New Jersey bounty hunter at the top of bestseller lists once again works its magic in Stephanie Plum's latest caper (after 2005's Eleven on Top). Stephanie, who freely admits her failings as a hunter of fugitives, faces a growing work backlog that threatens the continued existence of her job. Her clumsy efforts to clear some cases, along with the help of her outrageous colleague, Lula, result only in their adding another sad sack to the office payroll-a forlorn shoe salesman who's talked off a ledge by Stephanie's offer of a position as file clerk. Stephanie's ambivalence toward the two men in her life becomes harder to maintain when one of them, the mysterious Ranger, is accused of kidnapping his own daughter. Countless over-the-top scenes, including one at a funeral parlor, will delight longtime fans."/>
</I>
<I id='B5' A="Pirateology : The Pirate Hunter's Companion" B='|William Captain Lubber|William Captain Lubber' C='Candlewick' D='7/11/2006' E='32' F='0763631434' G='19.99' H='0'>
   <I id='B5D' Def='Desc' G='|Books.jpg|64|75|320|0|http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0763631434/ref=amb_right-2_177609501_1/104-5992118-7327169?n=283155|_blank' B="Aar! Hoist the sails for a lavish new discovery filled with treasures - a magnificent resource for pirate lovers everywhere. The eagerly awaited new title in the best-selling 'Ology series - more than 5 million sold worldwide!&#x0A;&#x0A;Step lively, pirate foes and fanciers! Mysterious booty found inside a long-lost sea chest, hidden for hundreds of years off the coast of Newfoundland, has just been uncovered for your enjoyment. Within these covers is the fascinating eighteenth-century journal of Captain William Lubber, an earnest soul who sailed the seas in search of the vicious female pirate Arabella Drummond. Prepare for a mesmerizing tale of the golden age of piracy - from storm-tossed sailing ships to tantalizing treasure islands, from pirates' flags and fashions to their wily weapons and wicked ways. An extraordinary find for pirateologists, here is a true and complete companion for the dedicated pirate hunter.&#x0A;&#x0A;Pirateology's special treasures include:&#x0A;- a stunning cover bearing a working compass and glittering gems-treasure map with a missing piece - for the canny reader to find &#x0A;- multiple flaps, maps, charts, and booklets harboring codes and clues&#x0A;- intricate drawings of ships' interiors&#x0A;- a packet of gold dust - a pocket sundial&#x0A;- a cache of pirate letters, pieces of eight- and a jewel as a final reward"/>
   <I id='B5I' Def='Info' A='From the Publisher' B='PIRATEOLOGY offers adventurers and treasure hunters, landlubbers and sailors alike heretofore hidden knowledge of the exploits of one wickedly daring woman pirate and the lore of pirate ships, weapons, dress, customs, codes, and pirate routes.'/>
</I>
<I id='B6' A='Judge &amp; Jury' B='|James Patterson|James Patterson, Andrew Gross' C='Little, Brown' D='7/31/2006' E='400' F='0316013935' G='27.99' H='0'>
   <I id='B6D' Def='Desc' G='|Books.jpg|48|75|80|0|http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0316013935/qid=1152281332/sr=1-1/ref=sr_1_1/104-5992118-7327169?n=283155|_blank' B="Bestselling author James Patterson returns with the #1 blockbuster thriller of the summer, an unstoppable novel of law and revenge.&#x0A;&#x0A;Senior FBI agent Nick Pellisante is closing in on the notorious mob boss &quot;The Electrician,&quot; when the scheduled sting goes spectacularly awry. Two FBI agents are dead, the boss is wounded, and Pellisante vows the Electrician's next move will be from a jail cell.&#x0A;&#x0A;Andie Echeverra, a part-time actress and a single, full-time mom, is assigned her next role as Juror #11 in the landmark trial against Mafia Don Dominic Cavello. Everybody is on edge. No one has ever crossed the man whose orders have made entire families disappear.&#x0A;&#x0A;Though Cavello's influence extends across blue uniforms and black robes, the case should be open-and-shut. But the legal system fails with devastating results, and Nick and Andie are the only ones left to seek justice. To stop the Electrician, they must take matters into their own hands. They are the judge and jury now.&#x0A;&#x0A;James Patterson spins an all-out heart-pounding legal thriller that pits two people against the most vicious and powerful mobster since John Gotti."/>
   <I id='B6I' Def='Info' A='From Booklist' B="Judge and Jury gets off to a slightly slow start but delivers plenty of twists and turns. FBI agent Nick Pellisante has finally done the impossible: captured Mob boss Dominic Cavello. The jury is selected and Cavello's trial progresses smoothly--it seems the conviction Pellisante is hoping for is within his reach. Several formerly loyal henchmen now sitting in jail strike deals with the prosecution and testify about the savage murders Cavello ordered, and Pellisante takes the stand to detail how Cavello shot two of his colleagues while trying to elude capture. But Cavello has hired Richard Nordeshenko, a methodical and calculating killer, to make sure the trial never concludes. Nordeshenko carries out his plan with brutal efficiency, leaving a wake of devastation in his path. Pellisante is crushed by the abrupt end of the trial and determined to make sure that the retrial isn't similarly derailed, but Cavello and Nordeshenko have an even more diabolical plan in store this time around. A compelling hero and a truly evil villain distinguish this exciting read. Kristine Huntley"/>
</I>
<I id='B7' A='Phantom' B='|Terry Goodkind|Terry Goodkind' C='Tor Books' D='7/18/2006' E='592' F='0765305240' G='29.95' H='0'>
   <I id='B7D' Def='Desc' G='|Books.jpg|49|75|400|0|http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0765305240/ref=amb_right-4_165736201_1/104-5992118-7327169?n=283155|_blank' B="On the day she awoke remembering nothing but her name, Kahlan Amnell became the most dangerous woman alive.  For everyone else, that was the day that the world began to end.&#x0A;&#x0A;As her husband, Richard, desperately searches for his beloved, whom only he remembers, he knows that if she doesn't soon discover who she really is, she will unwittingly become the instrument that will unleash annihilation.  But Kahlan learns that if she ever were to unlock the truth of her lost identity, then evil itself would finally possess her, body and soul.&#x0A;&#x0A;If she is to survive in a murky world of deception and betrayal, where life is not only cheap but fleeting, Kahlan must find out why she is such a central figure in the war-torn world swirling around her.  What she uncovers are secrets darker than she could ever have imagined."/>
   <I id='B7I' Def='Info' A='Review' B='"Wonderfully creative, seamless, and stirring."&#x0A;--Kirkus Reviews on Wizard&apos;s First Rule&#x0A;&#x0A;"Wonderful."&#x0A;--Kliatt on Stone of Tears&#x0A;&#x0A;"Each volume of the Sword of Truth... proves more difficult to review than the last. There are only so many ways of heaping praise on a series that gets better and better."&#x0A;--SFX on Blood of the Fold&#x0A;&#x0A;"...outstanding work...adrenaline and characters who actually behave like adults. Highly recommended."&#x0A;--San Diego Union Tribune on Temple of the Winds&#x0A;&#x0A;"...thoroughly enjoyable."&#x0A;--VOYA on Soul of the Fire&#x0A;&#x0A;"Mr. Goodkind&apos;s compelling prose weaves a magic spell over readers."&#x0A;--Romantic Times Bookclub on Faith of the Fallen&#x0A;&#x0A;"Near-perfect pacing, well-realized settings, and superior descriptive narrative."&#x0A;--VOYA on The Pillars of Creation'/>
</I>
<I id='B8' A='Cover of Night' B='|Linda Howard|Linda Howard' C='Ballantine Books' D='6/27/2006' E='352' F='0345486501' G='29.95' H='0'>
   <I id='B8D' Def='Desc' G='|Books.jpg|49|75|160|0|http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0345486501/ref=amb_right-5_185407001_1/104-5992118-7327169?n=283155|_blank' B="For breathless action, gripping suspense, and intense romance, bestselling author Linda Howard never misses a beat-and her thrilling new novel will have your heart racing.&#x0A;&#x0A;In the charming rural town of Trail Stop, Idaho, accessible to the outside world by only a single road, young widow Cate Nightingale lives peacefully with her four-year-old twin boys, running a bed-and-breakfast. Though the overnight guests are few and far between-occasional hunters and lake fishermen-Cate always manages to make ends meet with the help of the local jack-of-all-trades, Calvin Harris, who can handle everything from carpentry to plumbing. But Calvin is not what he seems, and Cate's luck is about to run out.&#x0A;&#x0A;One morning, the B&apos;B's only guest inexplicably vanishes, leaving behind his personal effects. A few days later Cate is shocked when armed men storm the house, demanding the mystery man's belongings. Fearing for her children's lives, Cate agrees to cooperate-until Calvin saves the day, forcing the intruders to scatter into the surrounding woods.&#x0A;&#x0A;The nightmare, however, is just beginning. Cate, Calvin, and their entire community find themselves cut off and alone with no means to call for help as the threat gathers intensity and first blood is drawn.&#x0A;&#x0A;With their fellow residents trapped and the entire town held hostage, Cate and Calvin have no choice but to take the fight to their enemies under the cover of night. While reticent Cal becomes a fearless protector, Cate makes the most daring move of her life . . . into the very heart of danger."/>
   <I id='B8I' Def='Info' A='About the author' B="Linda Howard is the award-winning author of many New York Times bestsellers, including Killing Time, To Die For, Kiss Me While I Sleep, Cry No More, Dying to Please, Open Season, Mr. Perfect, All the Queen's Men, Now You See Her, Kill and Tell, and Son of the Morning. She lives in Alabama with her husband and two golden retrievers."/>
</I>
</I>
</B>
</Body>
</Grid>